golly I say we got quite the harvest
this season wouldn't you say ha ha come
on now Papa you are crazy you can't
shove that up your ass we need to save
that for dinner why are you always doing
this I'm heading inside to check if
dinner is ready don't keep us waiting
for too long paw
you
[Applause]
I'm back from picking corn with paw
how's dinner coming along baby you won't
believe it
paw tried sticking the corn up his ass
again that old man's crazy
well don't leave me hanging like a
horseshoe Jarred hurry up and show me
all the corn you collected big boy
sweet baby Jesus I've never seen so much
corn in my entire [ __ ] life and your
pod was really going to stick all this
up his big ass well consider me
impressed I thought I told you to have
dinner done by the time I got back [ __ ]
what were you doing all day
were you having butt sex with the local
hillbillies
what in tarnation what's pause bedroom
door doing open Jeffrey please wait
don't go in there what in tarnation what
our pause overalls doing on the floor
huh you [ __ ] was my paw [ __ ] you in
the ass again this is the 4th time
this week I already told you if I catch
you having sex with my paw seven times
in a row you're outta here
yep you did say that Jared but you also
said this is only the 4th time so why
are you getting so riled up it's not my
fault that your paw really knows how to
spank my fat ass and treat me like he's
not a little cowgirl are you proud of
yourself being the local [ __ ]
what spawn doing outside he never stops
picking corn this early that old man
must think we're somebody else it looks
like he's ready for a fight
what should we do boss should we turn
back or should we risk taking him it's
fine Charlie
if this old man is looking for a fight
then we will gladly give him one
this will be my last morning for all you
city folk get off my farm in ten seconds
or I'm blowing all your brains out
too bad for you city folk I never
learned how to count fast to you go
confront the old man tell him we mean
him and has farmed no harm
are you [ __ ] crazy there is no way in
hell I'm going out there he's got a gun
what a coincidence so do I you [ __ ]
[ __ ] do you want to be a member of a
boys right
well the positions not free you got to
earn it if you want to be a member of
the cool kids you got to stop being a
little pushover [ __ ]
[Music]
so the three of you are the children of
Queen Aleena I can see the family
resemblance yes I did take that photo I
guess you could say that I'm a family
friend Wow your butt is so big you
really are your photos who are father's
or what that's right I suppose I should
tell you about him I kept you all
waiting long enough
[Music]
I should have told those kids about
their father when I had the chance I
should have told them everything but I
was too distracted by that girl's butt
cheeks and now the cause of that mistake
I'll probably never be able to tell them
anything who their father is the kind of
man he was not even his name if I die so
does the one chance of Sonic Manic and
Sonia finding their father that's right
I can't die here
I must tell them everything there must
be a reason God left me alive after I
fell from that cliff I must tell the
Sonic Underground everything they want
to know right now I am lucky the boys
think I am one of them I can use that
against them if I turn my back on God if
only for a little while and play the
role of evil then I will be able to
survive long enough to pass on this
information please put the gun down we
mean you no harm
[Music]
yee-ha
what is the Wild West this isn't the
person of color good get in the car you
[ __ ] cowboy you're coming with us
don't try any sudden movements or it'll
pop the cap in your ass Noah where are
you taking my paw you bastards
I can't believe pause actually gone it
feels like just yesterday he was beating
my ass for not digging up potato is fast
enough
hey Jared what the hell is that on that
there countertop
what in the world what are those
mechanical doohickeys the package says
that they are called walkie-talkies are
they some kind of modern trash
greetings Jared we hope we didn't scare
you too bad when we kidnapped your
father
who the hell are you people where did
you take my paw I want answers now quiet
we're the ones in charge here now if you
want your precious power back you will
do everything we say do you understand
[ __ ] it's funny that you think you
can't tell me what to do
Emma hillbilly [ __ ] I won't do [ __ ] I
see you have balls but if you don't do
what we say then your daddy is as good
as dead shut your piehole old man stop
it stop it leave my pot alone I do
anything you ask of me
I'll even wipe your smelly butt very
good I suppose all you needed to
cooperate was a little incentive let us
hope that we don't have to resort to
that method okay now let's get down to
business
I want you to kill my arrival my mortal
enemy the very man who made my life hell
Uncle Chuck
who the [ __ ] is Uncle Chuck forget that
we are losing precious time three do you
know the brother of art levees [ __ ] why
sure I do
Manic the Hedgehog right good to kill
Manic Hedgehog that is your mission you
have one week to complete this desk if
you don't well let's just say Charlie's
gonna [ __ ] your puppet in the ass who
the [ __ ] is Charlie the guy who's gonna
[ __ ] your puppet in the ass damn it all
no you can't do this
Manic is your friend and the brother of
this [ __ ]
bottom they will hunt you down I have to
do this if I don't then the boys will
kill paw this is the only way
everybody gives you inside
[Music]